[Music]
I think it's over 3,200 Partners all in
one place which for us is a you know a
dream come true the energy from the
community has been super positive uh the
level of questions the feedback the
conversations the people that I meet
here are really all across the board
there's people that are colleagues their
Partners um their friends uh you know
just the kinship amongst this group is
is really incredible uh sometimes
they'll be competitive that are you know
working hard against each other and they
come to this event they share best
practices they go to parties
together directions is quite literally
the hottest ticket in town for anyone in
the in the organization that works on
business applications in SMB so we have
10 different area sessions um most of
which are in local language but it's a
great opportunity for partners to meet
with their local Microsoft team so it's
very much about enabling each other
within the community
for me it's very much about um what
Partners take away from this and you
know how can we help Partners be that
extension of our team to our customers
new ideas new things we can do you know
we're never done we're always working
hard and so I just leave this event very
energized with what to do next